tripraja.com 2009-12-14

# :: Tripraja :: Privacy Policy- Tripraja.com

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of Tripraja.com site. By using this site, you consent to our "Privacy Policy" set out below. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the "Terms of Use Agreement" between you and Tripraja.com which by use of this site you agree to accept.

## The Information We Collect

**Profile Information:** At the time you apply to travel specialists using Tripraja.com website, you will be asked to complete a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about you (Registration Information).

**Statistical Information:** In addition, we gather aggregate statistical information about our site and users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth known as "Statistical Information"

Your profile statistical information will be referred to as "Collective Information"

## How We May Use Information

**General:** We use your information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content, layout and service specific for you. We may use your information to service your account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our users. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of collected information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential users. We may use your information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message.

**Profile Information:** All of your "Profile Information" will be shared with travel specialists registered with Tripraja.com and therefore accessible by any travel agency/ specialist on our network that you have chosen to apply to. We may use your profile information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which Tripraja.com determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the registration information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions.

**Statistical Information:** We use "Statistical Information" to help diagnose problems with and maintain our computer servers, to manage our site, and to enhance our site and services based on the usage pattern data we receive. We may generate reports and analysis based on the statistical information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. We may provide statistical information to third parties, but when we do so, we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission.

## Disclosure of Information

We reserve the right to disclose our "Collected Information" to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of Tripraja.com, our users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

We also reserve the right to disclose collected information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.

If we have reason to believe that a user is in breach of the "Terms of User Agreement" or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such user's collected information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to Tripraja.com or others.

## Co-Branded Relationships

**We have established relationships with other parties to offer you the benefit of other products and services which we ourselves do not offer.** We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our site, or through offering "co-branded" sites in which both ourselves and these other parties share the same uniform resource locator, domain name or pages within a domain name on the Internet. In some cases you may be required to submit information for purposes of registering or applying for products or services provided by such third parties or co-branded partners. The privacy policy of such other parties may differ from ours, and we may not have any control over the information that you submit to such third parties or co-branded sites. We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding to any offers, products or services provided by such other parties.

## Cookies

We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our site. It is not uncommon for websites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can be sent to your computer's hard drive only if you access our site using the computer. If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our site and in turn we may have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage.

## Minors

The site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our site and so we carry out the same "Privacy Policy" for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information.

## Security Measures

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information. No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site.

## Your Feedback

Tripraja.com welcomes your continuous input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you. You may send us your comments and responses to [support@tripraja.com](mailto:support@tripraja.com)
